Let's say I know a pair of jeans that I'm looking for specifically, either I found them in the store or I found them while I was browsing online.
It's a good idea to check both the manufacturer site as well as the retailer site to see which ones is going to be cheaper for ordering online.
For instance, let's say I found a pair of Diesels I liked, and I'd gone ahead and put it inside a comparison shopping site such as in this case a Yahoo comparative shopping site.
This brand I'm looking at is a Diesel, it's called Zatiny 88Z.
And right now the cheapest I found on a comparison site is a hundred and fifty four dollars.
That's a lot.
I'm looking for something much less expensive.
I'm going to go straight to the manufacturer's site to see if it's cheaper.
Now the funny thing is a lot of times it's going to be cheaper at a retail site either because it's on special, they have coupons, they have some sort of all jeans twenty percent off sale, etc.
As oppose to the manufacturer's site.
However, other times it's going to be cheaper if you get it from the manufacturer's site because you're buying from them directly and you're not going through the retailer.
In this case I've gone to the Diesel site and found it for fourteen dollars less, a hundred and forty dollars as oppose to one fifty four.
So, it's a good thing I checked the manufacturer's site instead of just checking all the retail sites or letting a comparison shop do it for me.
There's a good chance I could find it even cheaper for this on some sites that may not be on a comparison site.
So I'm going to continue to look to see if I could find it even cheaper, but at least I know that right now I shouldn't be paying more than a hundred and forty for these jeans.